그러니까 내 말은..
Look, I'm just saying...
페니는 이웃에 사는 사람 중 한 명이잖아요
Penny is one of our many neighbors,
이웃끼리는 가고 오고 하잖아요
and in our building, neighbors come and go,
자연스럽게 말이죠 복장 제한 없이요
it's very casual, no dress code.
예전에는 아침에 잠옷만 입고 3층을 어슬렁어슬렁 돌아다니다가
In fact, some mornings I'll just mosey down to the third floor in my pajamas
바타비디언 아주머니랑 시리얼도 먹었어요
and have cereal with Mrs. Vartabedian.
정말?
Really?
난 바타비디언 아주머니가 시리얼 먹으라고 한 번도 초대한 적이 없어
I have never once been invited to have cereal with Mrs. Vartabedian.
널 안 좋아하시거든
She doesn't like you.
스테파니는 수술해야 할 쓸개가 있고
You have a gall bladder to remove
나도 샤워를 해야 하고
and I have to get in the shower
페니도 옷을 입어야 하니까요..
and Penny has clothes to put on, so...